



Summary of Qualifications

Full Stack development and consulting with experience using a wide array of technologies to create actionable insights and grow software development initiatives leading to profitable business decisions.

Core Competencies

❖ Data Viz: HTML, CSS, JS, Streamlit **DevOps**: Github Actions, Jenkins

❖ ML Operations: H2O, Torch, Tensorflow

❖ Agile: Github, Azure DevOps, Jira

Apis: FastAPI, Flask, Node

❖ Data Analysis: R, Python

❖ Data Storage: Azure Blob, AWS S3

❖ Databases: Postgres, MongoDB, Redis

❖ JavaScript: React, Svelte, Vue, Angular

* Cloud: AWS, Azure, GCP

Certifications

Azure	AWS	Google Cloud
<u>Azure Cloud Intro</u>	AWS Cloud Intro	GCP Core Infrastructure
Azure Serverless Applications	AWS Cloud Technical Essentials	GCP Production Machine Learning

Experience

Guidehouse **Technical Lead Managing Consultant**

Atlanta, GA March 2023 to Present March 2022 to March 2023

(470) 540-3756

As lead on the Analytics & Infrastructure (AIA) Team, I was promoted at 1 year by coding developer tools for consultants producing millions in annual client revenue.

- Implemented FastAPIs for automation leveraging Web Apps and Apis across platforms of Github, Okta, Jira, Jenkins & Posit Connect containers to increase Infrastructure team profitability.
- Updated 30+ ML Puthon applications primarily with Torch & TensorFlow into Kubernetes on AzureKS.
- Developed data management schema for energy sector for Electric Vehicle & Solar in Azure Blob via custom R + Python packages.
- Deployed automation via FastAPI to connect Jira tickets to Service Now requests for efficient developer requests internally.

Pennsylvania State University **Full Stack Developer**

Remote **May 2021 to December 2021**

Organized and cleaned years of Graduate Student code for a cohesive module set of R shiny code to provide professors the ability to upload and assess students in real time with data storage in AWS S3.

WarnerMedia **Full Stack Developer**

Remote April 2021 to November 2021

Coded R Shiny apps, plumber APIs, and data pipelines to provide analyst with quality data and validation checks for accurate reporting all using R & Python with housing data in Snowflake + Azure Blob.

Projects

- Windows 98 Themed Portfolio deployed on Netlify written in vanilla JavaScript
- SaaS Startup deployed on Vercel written in React with Supabase Authentication
- YouTube Channel website deployed on **Azure Container Services**
- FastAPI portfolio with Jinia and DockerHub

Visit Windows98 App Visit CodePay Cloud View @majesticcoding Visit FastAPI App

McAfee R Shiny Developer

Remote November 2020 to March 2021

Contracted to scale and build shiny apps for massive data distillation for model building for enhanced cross sell of products in the McAfee portfolio via optimization of web effectiveness.

Coca Cola Beverages Florida Full Stack Developer

Remote August 2020 to November 2020

Contracted to redesign and scale an R Shiny app for a predictive application with a boasted decision tree model using Azure ML API predicting the potential revenue of prospective Coca Cola customers with outputs used to construct contracts with merchants.

Ovintiv (formerly Encana) R Shiny Developer Denver, CO August 2019 to April 2020

Contracted to build models and apps used to determine the best geographies to drill for oil and gas for predictive on well output, the associated costs and investment, ROI, Tax and related financial metrics.

EverCommerce Data Analytics Consultant

Denver, CO November 2018 to July 2019

Established data analytics for the parent company of over 30 subsidiaries with Software as a Solution applications for various verticals in the Small/Medium Business space working with KPMG on M&A activity.

Total System Services, Inc. Senior Market Research Analyst Denver, CO February 2018 to November 2018

Led the development of a newly formed Market Research/Analytics Department within the Merchant Services Division for one of North America's largest payment processors.

SKIM Group Analyst

Atlanta, GA January 2017 to February 2018

Worked with clients Unilever, AT&T, and Mercury Marine on 8 projects generating over \$500,000 in revenue.

Vizeum, Division of Dentsu Aegis Analytics Specialist Playa Vista, CA June 2016 to October 2016

Nielsen Intern/Analyst

Berry College

Glendale, CA
December 2015 to February 2016

Education

Clemson University

Clemson, SC

M.S. in Marketing, Market Research concentration

August, 2015

B.S. Psychology, Minor in History

Mount Berry, GA

Berry Men's Soccer Team, 4-year letter winner

May, 2014